In the game
2nd game
Thanks for your time
After singing for the last 2 seconds here.
Try a few more of these.
It's important.
It's hard to pitch.
We're shooting a music video for Foxy Grape today.
I'm the first one to shoot and I just shot the first cut.
The thing that surprised me was...
The set today was absolutely gorgeous!
It was like we were really in the world of the story.
It's like we're really in the world of the story, and we're able to shoot in such a world.
I'm sure we'll be able to create something great when it becomes a video.
I think we'll be able to see the complete form of the song "Foxy Grape".
We have a lot of work to do today, but we will do our best and make a good music video.
I hope we can make a good music video together.
That's all for now, this is Yoshida Kaname.
Today, we're starting with individual shots.
I'm going to start with a scene where I'm throwing darts and
I'm going to start with a scene where I'm throwing darts and doing it in a stylish way.
It really looks like throwing darts.
I've never played darts at all.
I've only played darts with a magnet when I was little.
I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to go in there and throw it.
Balance.
It's up.
Isn't this Basilow?
Let's get to work!
Cut!
Here's the cut!
Amazing.
We're pouring.
So this is the Foxy Grape disc concert single.
It's the first time we've done a poll on the four holes.
It has a different atmosphere from the usual local dances
and the tempo of the music is different from the usual local dances.
Everyone got into it and wore these costumes.
The costumes were dark, which you don't usually see.
However, they also had a beautiful suit that had a local Mai-like look to it.
We will do our best for the music video shooting today!
Let's go!
Good morning.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The grass is growing even though it's in my room.
It's not good.
We just finished shooting the image cut.
Yes, it's a really cool set.
It's a room, but there are grapes growing along the Foxy Grape title.
And there's a plaster statue of David Nikiranjilou.
I thought it was really stylish and cool.
There is also a dance scene, so I'm really looking forward to the finished version.
We haven't even shot the dance scene yet, but I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
It's so realistic!
You can't touch them!
The last part is a little scary.
It's scary.
It's like there's a break in the story.
Okay.
Oops!
No way.
Oh, it's Pris.
Fourth class?
This is male lumber.
But the other scores were lower, 3 and 4.
If you put it in the middle, that's what you get, because it's amazing.
But it depends on how you play the game.
Fifty. Fifty.
Here you go, 50.
I got 57.
Double double.
Triple.
Twenty-four.
Nice try.
Not one more time, zero more.
No more chances.
We don't have another chance, do we?
Yes, sir.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-two?
No, double eight.
That's 12.
Twenty-four.
Eight times three is 24.
Thirty-six.
Triple it.
Can I do it again?
Go ahead and beat my record.
But I was right in the middle.
You got it, didn't you?
That's great.
You're gonna need this.
Seven.
Okay.
Forty-three.
Oh, it's broken?Oh, it's broken?
No, it's not broken.
Well, it looks like it.
Stop.
You're a hell of a thrower, you know that?
Just a thousand more this way.
Oh, what?
This much.
Is that it?
You're a hell of a thrower.
You're supposed to throw it like this.
You're good. Go ahead.
Thank you very much.
Not at all.
Oh, but it's a two.
It was a two.
17 is a 2.
There you go.
You're good.
Nice try.
Middle of the bull?
Yes, the middle of the bull.
But beautifully.
There'll be a replay, I'm sure of it.
Oh, my God, it's so beautiful.
Low numbers and a winner.
That's what I'm talking about.
You know what?
You know...
God Shakari Hip Hop
has a little bit of a choreography
There's a TikTok choreography.
I'm going to start now.
First of all, I'm going to make a determined face.
I'm going to make a face.
Sorry.
The real switch is an important choice.
I'll get ready.
And then it begins...
Alps 10,000 Shaku
Let's do it!
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
So far...
I can do Alps 10,000 Shaku.
There's no site that teaches you how to do it by pretending.
I can't do this.
The Alps are 10,000 feet high.
Where's your hometown?
I went up to...
Folly.
Five.
Go with that.
FIVE
In, Tears of Moussonjauit
Moosun
Jau
Jauit
Ribbon
Moosun Jauit
Lovely
Tears of Seven Rounds of Tears
Glittery
Lakilaki
Twinkle Twinkle Lee
Raki Raki Raki
Kitsune
Kitsune.
This one?
Yes.
Tettetten.
Fox mania.
Much earlier.
Yes, yes, yes
Face
face
When you do this
Tettey ttee ttee ttee
Sei-no-sei
Tettey Tettey
five
blow fire
Moussonjauit
mousson
LOVELY
Lovely
seven shots of tears
Kira Kira Kira
Rakiraki
La la la la
I mean
Let's see...
Tettey Tettey
Lighter
Teen
Tettey TetteyTettey Tettey
Su阹
Tettehtten.
So karta kolcheib?
pipes
It's really KARTA Kolcheib!
First of all, Cs
South of
on
of tears?
No, no, no.
Parallel Cars of Tears
Sparkle
Eh, the timing of this move
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
One, two, three, four.
Toot-toot.
Yes, sir.
I can do it.
Toot-toot.
Hm.
Music.
Toot-toot.
Hm.
That's how you do it, music.
Quick, huh?
Music.
I can't set it up.
Start.
Oh, I see. It's still there.
That's the making of, right?
That's when you're doing it, right?
There's the song.
That's it?
Here we go.
Let's start with your song.
And I'll get ready.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Let's go
I got a bad one.
Yes, sir.
Moonsjite.
Lovely Lovely
Parallel cars
Sparkly Sparkly
La kira kira lala
Oh wow
You're so good!
so that's why
then go, go, go, go
I'm early
I've got an ex-pat here.
We'll do it together.
Yeah, that's right.
Just you and me, Joon.
What are you wearing, Joon?
I saw you eating that vent.
You were eating that vent.
I see.
Let me guess...
I'd like to take a hit, but...
It's just around the corner.
I have a place to sleep at home.
They've started shooting the music video, though.
FOXY CREPE
Hey, again.
We're shooting in a different atmosphere than usual.
Right now, we've just finished shooting a personal one.
We just finished filming.
I'm going to do a dance scene later.
It's been a while since I've danced.
I'm going to do some preparation.
I'll do my best.
Wow!
I'm going to do some martial arts now.
I'm going to do martial arts.
What?
Oh!
Did you do that?
No.
I did that one.
I heard you did "Apple Farmer Man.
What's next?
Masaya did martial arts.
What a surprise.
Oh, I'm so excited.
It's mine, so I'll see if I can get my costume dirty or not.
No, no, no, no, absolutely not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We're gonna do the dance scene later.
And when we do the liquid scene, we're gonna have to do the same facial contortion.
Get ready to smack me in the face.
Ready?
Here we go.
Ready?Ready.
Here comes the cut!
Cut!
When in doubt, play by the Shogi rules.
I feel like I can't play by the Shogi rules.
No, it's simple.
The book...
One or two more.
This one goes to the king.
This one goes to the queen.
Queen Scabbi.
But, well, I want to shoot mainly for the rap dialogue.
The rap dialogue.
Like, you're kind of throwing it from here to there.
Like a throwback.
Okay, you got it.
Okay.
You're acting like a liar.
What are you doing?
You look good from this angle, Masai.
Nice!
Hey, you!
It'll get better.
The dance scene...
I'd like to do it.
Ms. June.
How do you like this set?
What do you think of this?
It's...
Chaotic.
Oh!
Um...
It's a normal living room.
I don't know how it got to be like this.
How did it become like a jungle?
This is a deep mystery.
June... did you even think about that?
I'm surprised.
There must be a reason for this phenomenon.
I'll take the first row.
I think I'd better go a little further forward.
That's right.
A little more forward.
I'll probably go with that, but I'll definitely go a little bit further forward.
Okay.
I'm going to go out a little bit more.
And now for the MUF dance part.
Yes, sir.
Well...
At last.
A dance.
How do you feel?
Well, I'm feeling pretty good.
Foxy grape...
It's a great feeling.
But it's been a long time since I've been in a place like this.
It's amazing.
It sure is.
Reminds you a little of Shakespeare.
A little.
Seriously.
A little Shakespeare.
But that was about two years ago.
That's right.
I miss it.
Shakespeare, two years ago.
It's a little bit like...
It's so similar.
It's like, "I miss the old days.
You know, back then?
In the garden.
We used to jump around and take pictures.
We never got to see each other because of the Corona disaster.
Well, do you want us to take some pictures now?
Shall we?
Let's go see Mr. Tondoshimuki.
It's time for everyone to take a picture!
Okay.
What are you talking about?
Just jump.
Let's do it.
321, let's go.
Ho!
What are you doing?
I'm just checking to see if the camera got all the way down to your feet.
I'm sure it did.
LOL.
Good job.
Good job!
Please.
Good work.
Then, please.
And that's why I'm here.
You can also become a secret here!
This is Kaito Miyachika.
Thank you for your time today.Thank you for your long time today.
Thank you very much.
One, two, three.
Hello.
Happy Birthday.
Happy Birthday
Thank you.
Thank you
Yay.
Wait a minute.
Watch out!
You're crying.
Wait a minute, I'm kind of dangerous.
I'm in danger.
What happened?
Oh, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Well, I wasn't expecting a celebration.
Thank you so much.
I'm not going to cry like that.
But it made me a little bit emotional.
I was really moved.
I'm sorry, thank you so much.
I don't know...
I'm feeling weak and I'm eating.